<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://cules.space/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://cules.space/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-08-26T21:01:34+01:00</updated><id>http://cules.space/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Cambridge University Light Entertainment Society</title><subtitle>We are a group of Cambridge University students who produce comedy shows to raise money for charity, and take it to members of the local community who might not usually have the chance to see theatre - all this while having lots of (very) amateur dramatics fun!</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Easter 2020: Radioplay and Sketch show!</title><link href="http://cules.space/shows/2020/06/10/welcome-to-jekyll.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Easter 2020: Radioplay and Sketch show!" /><published>2020-06-10T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2020-06-10T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>http://cules.space/shows/2020/06/10/welcome-to-jekyll</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://cules.space/shows/2020/06/10/welcome-to-jekyll.html">&lt;p&gt;We’re very excited to announce the Cambridge University Light Entertainment Society’s (remote) Easter term productions: “In The Nick Of Time” - a comedy radioplay by Grace Beckett and Henry Weighill, and “Nothing To See Here” - a sketch show featuring sketches by Gregory Miller, Anna Trowby and Ido Rosen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a very brief hiatus, CULES is making a grand (albeit rather poorly timed) return. Though we are in uncertain and unprecedented times, CULES will always strive to bring a smile to your face and provide fun, silly comedy theatre where it is most needed. This Easter term, we will be raising money for The Trussell Trust, a charity battling hunger and poverty throughout the UK. Though our radio shows will be totally free to access, we invite you to donate whatever you can to our fundraiser. Anything is appreciated!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">We’re very excited to announce the Cambridge University Light Entertainment Society’s (remote) Easter term productions: “In The Nick Of Time” - a comedy radioplay by Grace Beckett and Henry Weighill, and “Nothing To See Here” - a sketch show featuring sketches by Gregory Miller, Anna Trowby and Ido Rosen.</summary></entry></feed>